Athary Lokhande



atharv1377@gmail.com



+918308841377



linkedin.com/in/atharv-lokhande-b9249b216

Summary

As a computer science professional, I have experience in open source projects, machine learning, and data analysis. I have worked on projects involving natural language processing, sentiment analysis of customer reviews, recipe recommendation systems, and face mask detection. My skills include Package Management, Shell Scripting, Virtualization, Storage Management, Python programming language, Linux, Data Science, SQL, and MATLAB.

Experience



Machine Learning Intern

Ignitus

Mar 2023 - Present (3 months)

machine learning project that intersects customer purchase behavior and natural language processing (NLP) as sentiment analysis of customer reviews. The goal of this project is to build a model that can automatically classify customer reviews as positive, negative, or neutral based on the text of the review and the associated purchase behavior of the customer (e.g., what product they bought, when they bought it, etc.).



Student Intern

department of scientific computing, modelling and simulation sppu

Nov 2022 - Present (7 months)

used linux, python (django) and some machine learning techniques for project (recipe recommendation system)

Education



Savitribai Phule Pune University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

2020 - 2022

project done

Face Mask DetectorFace Mask Detector:

Made a project on whether the person caught in the camera is wearing mask or not using some python libraries, OpenCV, Keras/TensorFlow, and Deep Learning.

Skills

Package Management • Shell Scripting • Virtualization • Python (Programming Language) • Linux • Data Science • SQL • Data Analysis • MATLAB • GPT-4